

□ 073 074 1743 | Iiamwears@fastmail.com | Imaliam-wears-4608a649

Personal Profile_

I have worked as an IT Professional for over ten years and I consider myself to be an enthusiastic, highly motivated, helpful person who enjoys challenges and gains satisfaction completing tasks to the highest possible standard. I work well within a team, but I also thrive working alone, utilising my initiative to ask colleagues for their expertise where necessary.

Software Projects

Simple 3 slot Casino game

NETENT DEVELOPER INTERVIEW QUESTION

April – June 2019

- This was a NetEnt challenge to build a small, full stack JavaScript application; a simple game which can display a random outcome generated
 on the server.
- Used Node.js, JavaScript, HTML and CSS to produce a working application.
- Frontend JavaScript frameworks were not allowed and ES6 was encouraged.
- Unit tests were created using the mocha & chai framework

Portfolio site

FREECODECAMP CHALLENGE June 2019

- A side project that is partly finished to present some of my frontend development skills.
- Developed using Bootstrap.
- Future improvements; make the site more responsive and add a resume page with JS.

Password Generator

PRIVATE ASSIGNMENT September 2019

- A side project that is partly finished to present some of my frontend development skills.
- Developed using HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- · Future improvements; Improve responsiveness, add functionality to generate random strings. Tidy up design

freeCodeCamp Challenges

VARIOUS SMALL HTML & CSS CHALLENGES

June 2018 - ongoing

- Survey Form
- · Product Landing page
- · Technical Documentation page

Education

Worcester College of Technology

Worcester, England

HIGHER NATIONAL DIPLOMA IN COMPUTING

2005 - 2010

Online

• I completed this course whilst working full time on the college's busy IT Helpdesk

Udemy (Colt Steele)
The Web Developer Bootcamp - 60% Complete

Jan 2019 - Ongoing

- Intermediate HTML & CSS
- Bootstrap
- jQuery
- Node.js & Express

WatchAndCode.com Online

PRACTICAL JAVASCRIPT Sept 2018

• A beginner course to build a strong JavaScript foundation for web development

freeCodeCamp.com Online

FREE ONLINE WEB DEVELOPMENT COURSE

Aug 2018 - Ongoing

Beginning with tutorials that introduce students to HTML, CSS and JavaScript, students progress to project assignments that they must complete.

September 27, 2019 Liam Wears · Résumé

Work Experience

NetEnt Stockholm, Sweden

Dec 2018 - Present & March 2016 - Dec

2017

SYSTEMS SPECIALIST

- Implementing Jamf Pro Suite for advanced and automated Apple Mac administration.
- · Seamlessly migrating all mailboxes from an on-premise Microsoft Exchange environment to Microsoft Exchange-Online.
- · Building a load balanced Remote Desktop environment for secure remote application delivery to end users.
- Automating routine manual tasks with PowerShell.

Canfor Vancouver, Canada

SERVICE DESK ENGINEER

June 2018 - Nov 2018

- Windows Server / Services Management. Active Directory, DFS, DHCP, DNS, FS.
- Automating routine tasks with PowerShell.
- Maintaining documentation of IT environment.
- Managing and maintaining corporate imaging solution
- · Diagnosing issues with network connectivity, SSL VPN connectivity and WIFI access for local and remote computers.

NetEnt Stockholm, Sweden

IT SUPPORT TECHNICIAN

Dec 2014 - March 2016

- Providing on-site and remote end-user technical support.
- Supporting Audio Visual and video conferencing equipment; Projectors, TV's, Microphones.
- Implementation and management of our Microsoft (WDS, MDT) and MacOS imaging solution.
- · Managing our ticket queue and prioritising tasks.
- Supporting OSX and Windows based machines both software and hardware.

OGL Computers Worcestershire, UK

IT FIELD & INSTALLATIONS ENGINEER

June 2010 - March 2013

- Providing customers with an excellent level of service and technical solution within target SLA's.
- Providing hardware and software support to a variety of different desktops, servers & laptops.
- Solving jamming and quality issues with a wide range of printers, faxes and scanners.
- Resolving networking issues including modem, router and firewall problems.
- Diagnosing and resolving Server issues, varying from UPS problems, service failures to failing backups.

Employment Gap _____

Ski Season in Banff Canada

Nov 2017 - July 2018

Last year I took a break from my career with NetEnt to pursue my ambition of working a ski season in Banff, Canada which was an amazing experience. Since returning to Sweden I have continued my progression with NetEnt and am now looking for a new opportunity within Stockholm's booming tech sector

September 27, 2019 Liam Wears · Résumé 2